renewalcoupon2014.com 2016-06-24

# Privacy Policy

Lock Coupons ([http://lockcoupons.com](http://lockcoupons.com/)) understands that privacy is important to its clients.

This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.

  * **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Lock Coupons collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Lock Coupon’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use its website. From time to time, Lock Coupons may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate.

  * **Cookies and Tracking Technologies**

Some of our Web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you’ve visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. We may use cookies to remember personal settings you have chosen at our website. In no other context do we use cookies to collect information that identifies you personally. Most of the cookies we set are automatically deleted from your computer when you leave our website or shortly afterwards.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our site is accessed. Our use of cookies and other tracking technologies allows us to improve our Web site and your Web experience.

  * **Protection of personal information**

We understands the importance of securing your personal information. We do not collect personal information. Our sites do not need to register or login.

  * **Changes to Privacy Policy**

The internet and data privacy best practice are both developing. We therefore reserve the right to revise this Privacy Statement at any time. If this Privacy Statement changes in any way, we will place an updated version on this page. Regularly reviewing this page ensures you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we will share it with other parties.

Email: lockcoupons#gmail.com
